Sumitra reporting
Sumitra I am familiar with your work I
look forward to seeing it in person my
purpose is to create order you are the
embodiment of chaos
doom fist you are mistaken only with
order can humanity evolve order chaos
means to an end
order and discipline that is the only
way to live
I sense a kindred spirit
you think I should have to work with a
street ruffian I'm not all that excited
about this arrangement either what you
wish car will never understand is that
people should be free
what do you call freedom is an illusion
that causes more harm than good
well you wish car will never understand
is that people should be free
what do you call freedom I call anarchy
vishka is building a better future for
Humanity you believe that I don't even
know what to tell you
you should return what you stole from
this car stole you need to go ask your
bosses where it all came from then we
can talk
this cars using you just like they use
my father you just wait
you'll see your father was a vishka
employee he understood our company's
vision a shame he never educated you
Helix should keep the peace in Vishk are
developments who we do not need an army
to keep the peace we prefer our own
methods
armor how positively medieval
I've it takes that is a compliment by
lady
armor how positively medieval last I
checked I didn't ask for your opinion
there's something on your dress no there
isn't
I am impressed I would not think such
crude creations actually function why
thank you I must admit I'm surprised
Symetra you speak of law and of order
but you must know that life is chaotic
by its very nature you'll be lectured
about chaos and disorder from a machine
a punishment for your crimes
becomes chaos